[music]
you're wrong uncle another batyr ford
and you hold your back like sausage up but you need
sausage with them tongue cool it'll be tastier but
me in
our house I know everyone I live in the attic
and I can see everything cat Matroskin my
name is this surname such my attic is being
renovated I have nowhere to live and you
only have one wrong sandwich was
at home and you have strength
come to me
your mother won't drive me away with enemies here is a
stick stand up for me
[music]
something smells of cat spirit here it's
like uncle Fyodor brought a cat well
one year won't bother us won't bother you won't
bother them
but think for yourself what benefit is there from this cat well
why necessarily benefit
what benefit for example yes yes
Nastya's picture the picture is very big benefit it
blocks the hole in the wallpaper what
benefit will there be from the cat he can catch mice maybe
no mice labs we'll get but if this
cat is so important to you please  choose or o
or I blew a lesson
[music]
I choose you I have known you for a long time
and I see this cat for the
first time
[music]
my dear parents mom and dad I
love you very much
but I also love animals
especially all kinds of cats yes and you do not
allow me to introduce them from afar so I am
leaving for the village and will live there your son
Uncle Fyodor and the cat
[music]
take off take me to live with you I will
guard everything cave why we ourselves do
not live anywhere then in a year moving to
us farms we will start a lot then
Matroskin keep quiet good dog never
bothered anyone let's better find out if there is a
free house in the village
give me there was I was one house I will show there no
one lives the owners moved across the river
and the spiders have pawns there no well what will you
take me to live with you or should I
come running later in a year we will take we will take three of us more
fun than you what is your name Sharik I am from
simple dogs low purebred and my name
is Uncle Fyodor and then from Russian surnames
such a very nice
[music]
be healthy thank you and you boy whose are
you where did you get to our village I am nobody's
I am myself boy
my own I came from the city it does not
happen that children are by themselves
children are necessarily somebody's
why does it not happen I for example code
to myself code my own I am my
own but actually why are you
interested and took it out to the police listen
no I am not from the police I am from the post office I am the
local postman Pechkin therefore I
must know everything that you deliver the mail
for example and what will you subscribe
I will subscribe to Murzilka and I about hunting
something and I nothing more about him and I
will save what are we all these mad
king without milk and so we can
die maybe we need to
buy a cow we need to get money from where
or maybe borrow from the neighbors and what will we give it back we
need to give it back we will give it back with
milk
if we give milk why then a cow then it
means we need to sell something and what and
something unnecessary in order to sell
something unnecessary we first need to buy
something unnecessary about us there is no money but
let's sell you wool this is how
so me  we won't sell anyone we'll
go look for treasure what is a warehouse
[music]
how did I not think of who now a
cow in a club and in a garden we can
all not work we can buy at the market
and in a store it's better to buy meat in a store
why there are more subtleties
[music]
hurray
warehouse
[music]
[laughter]
this jackdaw got caught he
stole my Olympic ruble
he needs to be taken to a clinic for experiments you
can't take him to a clinic he
deducted mine and teach me to talk why are
you carrying this in a chest we went for mushrooms
I again of course I again to hell with
books they would have gone with a suitcase
[music]
someone is to blame he allowed everything I'll be
spoiled he just loves animals that's why he
left with a cat there needs to be dogs in the house
cats and friends a whole bag
and all sorts of cartoons when sending
then the children shouldn't disappear then the
parents will start to disappear because I'm
tired at work anyway I barely have the
strength to watch TV and in general  Do
n't tell me your nonsense, auntie,
tell me how we can find the boy, we need to
print a note in the newspaper that the
boy is missing, his name is Uncle Fyodor, he is one
meter twenty tall, if anyone sees him, let them
tell us,
and we are also in vain, let his root be
useful, well, tell me who is
there, well, tell me who is there, we wish everyone around you has
nothing to do,
you should learn him a song or a
poem, songs and I can sing myself, but there is
no use from them, and from yours,
who is there, and what use is there, such as a
stranger will come when we are not at home,
well, he will start knocking on the door, he must
ask who is there, and the person will think that
someone is at our house and we have nothing, and he will
not steal, it is clear you
[music]
worked
[music] no
longer, I am the postman Pechkin, I brought a
note about your boy
[music]
I am the postman Pechkin, I am taking the horse to the note,
boy tulip tool,
I will read this, the stove brought a note about
your boy, that is there and .
[music] the
boy is missing blue eyes height
metro 20 his parents are looking for him the
finder will get a prize
bicycle don't grieve alteda
yes there are many such boys
maybe not few but they don't give a bicycle for
everyone
now I will measure your boy
[music]
my dad and mom I live well just
great I have everything yes oh
[music]
my dad and mom I live well just
great I have everything I have my own
house it's warm we live
one room and a kitchen I
miss you very much
especially in the evenings and my health is not
so good my paws ache
till the tail falls off and the other
day I started to shed my
old fur is falling out don't even go into the house because the
new one is growing clean and
silky so my hairiness has
increased goodbye your son uncle
ball
[music]
that his
hairiness has increased he can now
sleep in the snow in winter I don't understand anything maybe we've
gone crazy
maybe our hairiness has increased and
we can sleep in the snow
if we've gone crazy then no  both of them
go crazy at once one by one it's only the flu that
everyone gets sick together hello I'm
postman Pechkin
from Prostokvashino it's you who give bicycles for
boys
[music]
it's your fault that Uncle Fyodor got sick
almost in most cases why why did you
give him cold milk to drink you
bragged about a thousand wahl how cold my milk is my
cow gives you no need to
buy a refrigerator yours what kind of weather yours are at home they sit only strangers watch TV shos we won't open the door open it's my mom and dad who arrived [music] see what they've brought your child to they need to be immediately taken to the clinic
for experiments
[music]
where are your raspberries
here they are please oh I didn't know that
cats are so smart I thought they can
scream not only on trees
think about it I can also embroider and on a
typewriter too
[music]
you son do as you wish but we'll take you to the city you'll need care
and if you want to take a cat or a balloon
or someone else we won't object we won't we
matroskin
come with me i went to kv-1 and
my cow farm supplies for the winter
hotel ball we will stay better he comes to us
on vacation and visits on
weekends
[music]
here take it you will have more fun with him
from there
[music] having
accepted oh how inconvenient
you completely forgot about pechkin
and right he is so naughty excuse me
why was I naughty because I did
n't have a bicycle and now I will immediately
start to get kinder and get some kind of animal
to live hung you come home
she is happy to see you
[music]
come about just class
[applause]
[music]
and I'm being stupid and there is
nowhere to go from your milk
sergio blow all the basins and milk are busy
0 in the washbasin this is milk and what here I
will get a second cow and wash how and how to get
less dirty and in general
some and with my tongue they which even
mice eat
and if your cow remembering I was she
hugged the code
for water, carbonated Pepsi-Cola for example
or kvass and if everything was in cubes and Bale
I would have gotten busy long ago and will get busy
I'm going to the entrance now and it's not a pity for you to
shoot the animals it's a pity well and if it's not your
instinct that wakes me up I was drawn into the forest
with terrible force and the animal by the way is
created to be hunted I'll be
back soon I'll shoot something tasty
so Uncle Fyodor and all the spaniels could see me
unhappy
what letter is this and this well how could it
not be this letter and this is when I've
had enough I'm tired of my life
completely without a ray of hope and I live like a
peasant serf
here my God the bill and therefore I have 4
evening silk dresses but nowhere to wear them
no everything is decided we're leaving tomorrow for the
Kurumi resort we have a wonderful house there is
Prostokvashino
just think no one came it's
our dad gone crazy he won't let us go to the resort
I don't want to go to the resort either
I Prostokvashino why  and what am I going to
do with your yogurt
evening dress chop wood or
charm bulls enough would I have
worked with a frying pan
and now I want to go to a resort to relax
[music]
boy he believes correctly he is better off in the village
he doesn't have evening dresses
[music]
sit down hunter I'll give you a ride
thank you Uncle Pechkin and how are you a hunter
you shoot well and what if I
throw my hat chemistry you'll get and
throw your hat in an hour
nothing will be left of it only girls
[music]
what happens it's not hunting anymore it's
fishing it turns out
and ture throw down your weapon and come up to the surface
quickly yes I would be glad to throw
Matroskin will rip my head off with a gun you have
paid money and my life is free
everyone consider that I drowned
[music]
note about a boy
with us and a boy this is nothing he
lives in our city my favorite cat
comes back the
hunter probably drags prey
[music]
only from different dogs to
pull out of the river and  I didn't ask to be
pulled out I may not have drowned at all and I
may have been scuba diving
[music]
you for our balloon oh this balloon we have a
hunter found a
method now no income
expenditure days too to do with it already without
capture it will disappear will dry up all services no
then courageous to make a sled dog out of
it and we'll buy a cart we'll
put the earlobe on it to the market grottoes with it we'll
Makosh Walter Reyza Zharyk do you want we'll make you a
sled dog and do what
you want I want something equally life is not
sweet to me no no no I'm writing I'll send mom and dad a
camera gun for the balloon
this hunt and you don't need to kill animals
[music]
[applause]
darling let's quit your lesson and let's go
to yogurt be patient I'm a lion evening
dress on the sofa and there are still two left well the
boy may be business is bad without
him it's bad for him there he
has such a code to which you have to grow and grow
he follows him like a stone  wall if
I had such a code maybe I would never have married
[music]
our cow had a calf from my
pathetic finger well what friends let's take
him to the house emom home only mom
but I wonder whose he is like the Czechs he is ours but
not ours the cow since I am
state to go out for rent took that
means the calf is state ball
ball help and please cows by
states and all that she gives milk
or calves I too here you uncle Fyodor samsa
whether if we rent a refrigerator di
ramon tea state right Santa
Claus which he earn tea frost
ours for skill for la rosa and we take
chose let's take one cow albino for it turned
out shark on the receipt cow
red 1 took one on the receipt and we
will shove about that to violate the shuttle
and you will not catch at all to buy so take it
forever with the calf I will never part with my Murka
and now twice
if I become
[music]
Gavryusha
lie at
your place give a cobriyu shop
[music]
I came on business and you butt heads we have what to do
with my hat
not a hat 1 and ventilation it has how many holes
and on what business did you come
I brought you a parcel so I brought you and no
yes because you don't have documents it's too early
you still have a document and we
won't put documents for tailed ones at all and why did you
bring the parcel and for those who do so stripes 1 parcel
arrived it needs to be brought arash
there are no documents it's not necessary for a
nutritional week to go parcel
what documents my documents and
documents always have a seal sometimes
you have a seal on the tail there are no pauses and it is
possible to forge
[music]
this is probably me a photo gun came for
no more big money costs yes that's what I
came up with
that we have the same box on the wild ones and when he will
have to again what is it I the postman
Pechkin brought the parcel only I brought you June
yes because you don't have documents and we
without the parcel and ourselves did not take it from you
why  boys what kind of shoe polish is it and
ordinary shoe polish to which you
clean your shoes there all this who sent you so much
shoe polish are you opening a shoe polish booth this is
my uncle who drew it he lives in a
heap for anyone shoe polish or not shoe polish but
I will not give you the parcel I am
not a fool and you brewed it there and I am here
Malkova and myself and I will ask you
our bird not to run oh come on you are angry - then
go and put up with me better all he is on the table
[music]
I ask comrade Pechkin
please sit down [music]
children are not
anti candies are very wonderful
[music]
here and there this is
my candy the question why are you there and
people are greedy for other people's goods share
now you will be a photo hunt and
will be engaged in animals and photographs in different
magazines Anya where they pay more blouse
tea Uncle Fyodor
hold on we will arrive soon only one dress
left
dad and mom
[music]
what a stupid 10 I spent half a day
running after her to take a picture
now you spent another half a day after him
why the picture
[music] congratulations on your
arrival
let's first
sort out the conflict what kind of conflict is
this attack look what they did with my hat
now it's good to
throw away the vermicelli
listen comrade Pechkin and you keep quiet there are three like
you on a hat nato okay
okay there are some vodka things for you a hat
calm down and just please give me a
field post and we will have a naval one
let me snap a picture of you from under a gun
no need for me from a gun I can
only start living start
retiring yes I understood a lot
if I had a second life I would be
checking the
curdled milk here
[music]
[applause]
what's going on outside it's the end of the twentieth
century
and in our house there is one pair of felt boots in two
and why did it turn out like this - what is
yours  there are no funds that is,
you don't have enough money we have funds we
don't have enough brains
I said there to the hunter buy yourself a
small spoon what he
[music]
went body bought they say beautiful it was
he without thinking and did we have
national village clothes in winter what a
small wadded pants sheepskin coat and a
fur hat we don't even have students in sneakers in winter
he was a blockhead he was without you tell them
about it
open his eyes so that it
clears up I can't we haven't talked to him for two days
not two but three now it's not a problem you can
send a letter through Rama that's what the post office is what you
can't say then
in the letter they write to you how you are a
simple form or a simple congratulator simple
air what his points don't want I don't want to
spoil
you I don't need anything from you I don't have
simple ones not only to congratulate and here are the
operations expenses not pro 2
well let's put yours or
and that's right
if the addressee's congratulatory form
first you have to congratulate I'm a
blockhead to you and then describe to you the
usual about the weather
[music]
wow good snowstorm two days  howls
for the whole hunt snowed and you keep quiet
comrade pierce
will write an answer about your breed
write and I will not write an answer to him I
teach I will throw a poker at him so that he
responds and why throw
if there is mail now we will pack it and
give it to the cat the same bandy role turns out
[music] they
sent you a poker by parcel they
wanted to launch you what what can you hear I will
launch it in a minute more than a kilogram it turns
out it is a parcel now we will deliver it
and if you roll a barrel on him for
years already a container take your brain it
turns out this is a trans agency
deals with
boobs
[music]
how tired I am of all this our apartments
I have a TV show to change
what is where when is called here later to my husband and you will
not understand what is lying where and when will
all this end and in general from your
gasoline all my flowers have wilted
it and there is no gasoline the flowers have wilted usually in
those houses where the atmosphere is very strict and
ours is too cheerful life these
fedor and ping-pong
and  you play chess and bought an old Zaporozhets that's
already fallen apart, I don't know what
else you're missing, we asked each other
and decided that we absolutely need to
get 2 children somewhere, to take the
term off, and
never be angry, and for the New Year we want to
go to Prostokvashino
if that's what you want, you
can go as much as you want, your Prostokvashino,
but I can't, I have performances at the
New Year's Blue Light, the
last electric train was wet, of course I love
nature, but not to the extent that I would ride in a
concert dress on electric trains
in Prostokvashino, it's freezing
there now, you need to put on a concert quilted jacket
and a concert one, I
wonder how my Sharik with Matroskin is doing,
and the Ministry of Communications is just Kvashin SKA and the
department is a
talking letter, the first time I've received something like this, I
wonder what Sharik with
Matroskin is starting to divide property, they'll
soon start sawing the stove, and then they'll make stoves out of used
Toyotas
[music]
oh, how good that you came to
give us an urgent telegram to Sharik, please
fill out the form, felt-tip pen,
Uncle Fyodor will arrive soon  .
urgently take my felt boots
go to the forest for a Christmas tree and 4 words and delivery is
50 kopecks from you and women in labor share
you have received a telegram will you
write an answer I will not I have no money and you will look in your
pockets and from my pockets
yes no I will draw him an answer
[music]
well what is this what kind of
folk art is this
Indian national folk hut fig
you call it the same we can
say found it in the trash washed cleaned
touch bottom so and he draws us a film their
best Uncle Fyodor instead of you got a turtle in a
box and I feel sorry for chopping down the trees
if everyone starts chopping down trees for the New Year
instead of Liza
only stumps will remain icons of old women it's
good when in the forest there are only stumps in general
my why is this stupid they sit
can and what will the birds do hares the
nypd thought porn hares to think and
who will think about us admiral advance 1
Kruzenshtern and let me ask
in order to improve education
and who will be here Ivan Fyodorovich
Kruzenshtern and do not know about only so the
passage was called on which my
grandmother right on probably was not like you
he was a good man since the
steamship was named after him and he would not have cut down Christmas trees no, there are
extras here
[music]
here comes the New Year soon
the clock is striking it seems to me it is not the clock striking
the actuators are knocking on the door with a foot come in
guess
Olya admiral Ivan Fyodorovich Kruzenshtern
man and steamship
well you are already completely there someone
coming uncle Fyodor he car networks
well we can't get through the road started
[music]
but came in sled dogs with I heard about would have
left sled cats first board and
sled postmen have you met at what
nothing we have in winter such roads and such weather
that sled academicians are already meeting I
saw myself I chose and I increasingly notice that
I seem to be someone under the name of the seas
and I do not dream of
televisions  nature replaced me
what was yesterday it's time for me to forget
tomorrow tomorrow they are neighbors to me
friends no one will recognize and me they me
strange some kind of tuning
table you have in circles and this is not a table for
them this is all overgrown with cobwebs they have such a table on
each pot
and on the stove even since
they don't talk
and we have already made peace to die when food
theaters attacked the snow because
joint work for my benefit he and to
unite Trushkin since everything
ended well for you have a pleasant year and
aren't you with us there will be a calculation at his lips and
and don't persuade now in our time the
main decoration of the table is
flowers let the TV and it shows your Putin
I'll go now do
n't leave the TV would definitely
fix it today our mother head model
Kia will be shown only under the
guise
but there is water wonderful living
real Christmas tree let's and we still have a lot of
old things for their sake to decorate the Christmas tree
[music] I
ask for attention please do
smart faces she you photo hunt I'm starting
what kind of you  to Moscow needs decided dad of the
second child to get well and well before
fur coat motorcycles got
and now children have started to get what
joy of your division many one uncle with a
big moustache gave
flowers I would give this uncle with big
ears tweaked the ears I
will show this uncle here he is here he is this
insidious type of
civilian appearance at this one sits and
this is the leader of mother's
amateur performance clearly noise will be again
only this is all in vain
on your TV the sound does not work for
this performance for six months prepared no no no
no about
yourself your mother and here and there I
convey what technology has reached it is not
technology that has reached
but I myself got here on skis and the concert was
recorded on film I told you that I
simply cannot live without our
Prostokvashino
poured winters in cities and villages and
we would never have known these merry days the kids would not have circled
around the snow woman
[music]
[applause]
this will pass we share the
channel with the most favorite cartoons
choose what you want to watch cartoons for
kids cartoons for older children
multi-episode my most famous
cartoons
[music]
choose if the buttons don't work the
key she drowns the menu player
[music]
she
she 2
[music]